BENJAMIN DELTENRE

WEB DEVELOPER

- benjdelt@gmail.combenjdelt.github.io/
- **6** 604-762-5243
- **♀** Vancouver BC
- in benjdelt
- benjdelt

Skills

LANGUAGES

JavaScript

Python

Ruby

HTML

....

CSS

C

TOOLS & LIBRARIES

Node.js

Express

React

Django

JQuery

Ruby on Rails

Flask

Bootstrap

Sass

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

July

2018

2007

to

Git

Education

Oct. Development
2018

Sept. IEPSCF Ath2004 Flobecq
to Bachelor
Sept. Accounting

Labs

Lighthouse

Diploma Web

Summary

Full Stack Web Developer with a passion for building apps and creative **problem solving**. I bring a strong focus to details and good time management skills from my **6 years of experience in the government finance sector**. I am a dedicated life-long learner always eager to discover innovative ideas. Fluent in **English** and **French**. *Legally entitled to work in Canada*

Experience

Shuup Vancouver, BC Junior Developer Feb. 2019 to Current

Multi Vendor Marketplace Platform and Custom Development Services Tech Stack: **Python, Django, JavaScript, LESS/SCSS/CSS, ReactJ**S

- Participated in **Open Source** development
- Developed add-on as a django app
- Managed ticket progress through Jira
- Wrote user documentation

TalentMarketplace

Vancouver, BC Oct. 2018 to Current

Volunteer Web Developer TalentMarketplace is an online, project professional recruitment platform.

- Tech stack: Django, React, PostgreSQL, TensorFlow
- Utilized **Git source control** through Bitbucket repository to pull, branch, push code and create pull requests
- Managed ticket progress through backlog in an Agile sprint development environment
- Robustly **resolved bugs and implemented features** on an existing, enterprise code base to quickly deliver system enhancements that **reached thousands of users**
- Thoroughly QAed (white box tested) all code to have a ticket return rate of 0%

Wallonia-Brussels Federation

Brussels (Belgium)

Expense Controller

July 2012 to June 2018

The French-speaking Community / Wallonia-Brussels Federation exercises its competencies in the French language region of Belgium and in regard to the institutions that fall under its purview in the bilingual Brussels-Capital Region.

- Effective task prioritization to meet tight deadlines under pressure
- Worked as part of a **team of 4 controllers** to control subsidies and public contracts for the whole Federation
- Implemented **unique procedure** for different functional departments to harmonize control operations
- Guided accountants for their budget requirements
- **Inspected** public contracts and subsidies before charging the budget for a total of **8 billion euros** per year

Projects

<u>Tinee</u> Nov. 2018 to Dec. 2018

URL shortener built with **Mongo**, **Express**, **React** and **Node**. The basic functionality of shortening links and copying them is available to unauthenticated users. Logged-in users have their shortened links automatically saved.

InForm Sept. 2018 to Oct. 2018

Full stack web app built with **Node, Express, PostgreSQL** and **React**, InForm is a Form Building and Document Management system for trades companies. Users can build customised forms for staff to fill out, and once they've been submitted, Foremen and Managers can easily access those forms and stay up to date.

ChattyApp Sept. 2018 to Sept. 2018

A full stack chat web app built with **Node**, **Express** and **React**. It allows users to communicate in real time, recognizes image urls in messages and displays them as images.

Tut Bucket Aug. 2018 to Aug. 2018

Full stack web app built with **Node, Express, PostgreSQL, jQuery** and **Bootstrap** that allows learners to save learning resources like tutorials, blogs and videos in a central place that is publicly available to any user.